We've already seen how much visualizations can
لقد رأينا بالفعل مدى قدرة المرئيات على
enhance the amount of information we're able to understand about our data.
تحسين كمية المعلومات التي يمكننا فهمها حول بياناتنا.
Tableau takes this another step further,
يجري Tableau هذه الخطوة الأخرى الإضافية،
by allowing anyone within a company to ask and answer questions about a dataset.
من خلال السماح لأي شخص داخل الشركة بطرح أسئلة بشأن مجموعة بيانات والإجابة عنها.
These visualizations can be exploratory,
يمكن أن تكون هذه المرئيات استكشافية،
or explanatory in nature.
أو تفسيرية بطبيعتها.
But the real key is how much faster these insights can be found,
لكن السبب الحقيقي يكمن في مدى سرعة العثور على هذه الأفكار،
due to the interactive nature of Tableau.
وذلك بسبب الطبيعة التفاعلية لـ Tableau.
The best way to learn any new tool,
أفضل طريقة لتعلم أي أداة جديدة
is for you to use it yourself.
هي استخدامها بنفسك.
However it can be hard to get started in a new environment.
ومع ذلك يمكن أن يكون البدء في بيئة جديدة أمرًا صعبًا.
Therefore, this class is structured in a way,
لذلك، يتم تنظيم هذه الدورة بطريقة،
where you will first watch one of us here at Udacity demonstrate a task in Tableau.
حيث ستشاهدون فيها أن أحد أفراد Udacity يشرح مهمة في Tableau للمرة الأولى.
The next concept following each video,
سيحتوي المفهوم التالي لكل مقطع فيديو
will hold text and images about the previous video.
على نص وصور عن الفيديو السابق.
Many students prefer this because it's easier to search using control F,
يفضل العديد من الطلاب هذا لأنه من السهل البحث باستخدام control F،
or some other text finding functionality,
أو بعض الوظائف الأخرى للبحث عن النص،
rather than finding the right spot in a video.
بدلاً من البحث عن النقطة الصحيحة في مقطع فيديو.
However, if you're ready to jump in and explore directly following the video,
ومع ذلك، إذا كنتم مستعدين للانتقال إلى مقاطع الفيديو التالية واستكشافها مباشرةً،
feel free to skip the text,
فلا تترددوا في تخطي النص
and dive right into the quizzes on the next concept.
والاطّلاع على الاختبارات في المفهوم التالي.
The quiz portions are the key to your mastery of Tableau.
إن أجزاء الاختبار هي سر إتقان برنامج Tableau.
The more you are doing,
كلما بذلتم مجهودًا أكثر،
the better you will get at Tableau.
أصبحتم أفضل في استخدام Tableau.
This is the essential element to gaining confidence with this tool.
هذا هو العنصر الأساسي لكسب الثقة في هذه الأداة.
Sometimes, the text, video,
في بعض الأحيان، لن تكون النصوص ومقاطع الفيديو
and quiz, won't be exactly the same.
والأسئلة متطابقة تمامًا.
But they will all use the same tools,
لكنها تستخدم جميعًا الأدوات نفسها،
and each is aim to give you practice using a particular part of Tableau.
ويهدف كل منها إلى منحكم تدريبًا باستخدام جزء معين من Tableau.
This lesson might look a bit daunting,
قد يبدو هذا الدرس مملًا بعض الشيء،
but really there's a lot of repetition of material,
لكن في الحقيقة هناك الكثير من تكرار المواد،
just depending on how you learn best.
ويرجع ذلك إلى الطريقة التي تتعلمون بها على أحسن وجه.
Researchers suggest that you learn best by doing.
يقترح الباحثون أنكم ستتعلمون على أحسن وجه من خلال التطبيق العملي.
So let's get started with that.
لذا دعونا نبدأ بذلك.